Next notice
Like Takoyaki Cocona.
I see.
What about you, Ms. Kanako?
Oh, wait, is it me? I'm...
So you're a producer, Kanako?
Yes, I am.
She gave me a lot of advice.
I think I was able to speak without being nervous.
At first
Kettle and Idol
Here we are again today!
Born in Mima form, born and raised in Stardust
I'm Yakan-kun, born and bred in hot water supply.
Today's guest will arrive at your doorstep at the beginning of the day!
This is an idol!
From Ebisu City Junior High School, number 15.
Nanahi Kazami from Ebisu Junior High School.
It's nice to meet you, Kazami-san.
What a surprise.
It's been a year and a half since you joined us, hasn't it? Yes, a year and a half has flown by.
It's been a year and a half. Yes, I've had a lot of experiences, not only in live performances, but also in magazine shoots and on the radio.
Are you satisfied? Yes, 2022 was quite fulfilling for me because I had a lot of gigs, including some live shows with other bands.
It was a lot of work, but I think Ebichu had a lot of live performances in 2022.
I see... So it was the 10th anniversary... And you two...
I know it's hard to say... but I didn't think I'd be your senior in just one year.
I was very surprised, and I've been helped a lot by the older members, so now I don't have the title of a new member anymore, so I have to do more by myself.
I was glad that the new member was the youngest, wasn't I?
And even though they were the same age, they were one year older than me, so it was a big problem to figure out what to do.
It's quite difficult, isn't it?
But also, since they are our seniors, there are a lot of things we don't know, and we can't really teach them.
I thought it would be better for me to do what I can do and grow together with them by watching their backs.
I don't think I can tell you what to do here.
I see.
Not at all.
Watch my back!
Yes, I'm doing what I have to do.
I'll do what I have to do, and we'll grow together while watching each other.
Isn't that a bit professional!
I think so.
Why is nature like this?
I'm already...
I think Yuriko Kaniuji is growing up.
No, no, no, no, I think you're right already.
Wait a minute, that... I love it now.
You know, you said it in such a cute and serious way.
This program is...
Monta-san
Iate, Anezo
I love Nonoka-chan, Coco-chan
Katsu-san
We thank Mikan Arai for providing us with this program.
Thank you very much.